Fox Movietone Newsreel Collection - World War II Paper Records
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Dope Sheets, 1922-1946, undated (Box 237-254, OV1-OV7)
  - 57-1 to 57-50, 1945 July-1946 January (Box-folder 253/3)
  - 57-51 to 57-85, 1945 December-1946 February (Box-folder 253/4)
  - 57-86 to 57-99, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 253/5)
  - 57-100 to 57-144, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 253/6)
  - 57-145 to 57-182, 1945 November-1946 June (Box-folder 253/7)
  - 57-183 to 57-199, 1946 February (Box-folder 253B/1)
  - 57-200 to 57-247, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 253B/2)
  - 57-248 to 57-283, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 253B/3)
  - 57-284 to 57-299, 1946 February (Box-folder 253B/4)
  - 57-300 to 57-348, 1946 January-February (Box-folder 253B/5)
  - 57-349 to 57-370, 1946 February (Box-folder 253B/6)
  - 57-371 to 57-389, 1931 July-1946 February (Box-folder 253B/7)
  - 57-390 to 57-405, 1946 February-March (Box-folder 254/1)
  - 57-406 to 57-428, 1946 February-March (Box-folder 254/2)
  - 57-429 to 57-450, 1946 February-March (Box-folder 254/3)
  - 57-451 to 57-499, 1945 December-1946 March (Box-folder 254/4)
  - 57-500 to 57-531, 1930 May-1946 March (Box-folder 254/5)
  - 57-532 to 57-555, 1928 July-1946 March (Box-folder 254/6)
  - 57-556 to 57-599, 1930 January-1946 March (Box-folder 254/7)
  - 44-694 to 46-203 (Box OV1)
  - 46-221 to 46-986 (Box OV2)
  - 47-003 to 47-430 (Box OV3)
  - 54-026 to 56-663 (Box OV4)
  - 56-737 to 57-343 (Box OV5)
  - 57-347 to 57-582 (Box OV6)
  - 54-367 (Box OV7)
- Continuity Sheets, 1941-1946 (Box 887-889B)
  Synopses of newsreels distributed to theaters. The boxes and folders that contain the Lavenders subseries of materials are heavy due to enclosing the majority of documents in Mylar for protection.
  Arranged chronologically, with volume and release numbers.
  - Lavenders, 1941-1946 (Box 887-889)
    Includes individual story number(s) that make up each newsreel.
    - 24/1 to 24/35, 1941 [September]-1942 January 6 (Box-folder 887/1)
    - 24/36 to 24/51, 1942 January 8-March 3 (Box-folder 887/2)
    - 24/52 to 24/104, 1942 March 5-September 3 (Box-folder 887/3)
    - 25/1 to 25/33, 1942 September 8-December 29 (Box-folder 887/4)
    - 25/34 to 25/51, 1942 December 30-1943 February 26 (Box-folder 887/5)
    - 25/52 to 25/90, 1943 March 2-July 11 (Box-folder 887/6)
    - 25/91 to 25/104, 1943 July 16-August 30 (Box-folder 887/7)
    - 26/1 to 26/55, 1943 September 3-1944 March 10 (Box-folder 887/8)
    - 26/56 to 26/104, 1944 March 13-[August] 29 (Box-folder 888/1)
    - 27/1 to 27/44, [1944 August 31]-1945 January 27 (Box-folder 888/2)
    - 27/45 to 27/77, 1945 February 2-May 24 (Box-folder 888/3)
    - 27/78 to 27/104, 1945 May 27-[August 27] (Box-folder 888/4)
    - 28/1 to 28/54, [1945 August 30]-1946 March 5 (Box-folder 888/5)
    - 28/55 to 28/104, 1946 March 8-August 26 (Box-folder 888/6)
    - 24/1 to 24/104, 1941 [September]-1942 September 3, Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889/1)
    - 27/1 to 27/104, 1944 [August 31]-1945 [August 27], Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889/2)
    - 28/1 to 28/104, [1945 August 30]-[1946 August 26], Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889/3)
  - Summaries, 1942-1945 (Box 889-889B)
    Includes length of footage contained on each newsreel.
    - 24/35 to 25/34, 1942 January 5-December 29 (Box-folder 889/4)
    - 25/35 to 25/104, 1943 January 4-August 30 (Box-folder 889/5)
    - 26/1 to 26/104, 1943 September 2-1944 August 28 (Box-folder 889/6)
    - 27/1 to 27/104, 1944 August 31-1945 August 27 (Box-folder 889/7)
    - 28/1 to 28/36, 1945 August 30-December 27 (Box-folder 889/8)
    - 25/1 to 25/104, 1942 September 7-1943 August 30, Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889B/1)
    - 26/1 to 26/104, 1943 September 2-1944 August 28, Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889B/2)
    - 27/1 to 27/104, 1944 August 31-1945 August 27, Photocopies. With MTA numbers. (Box-folder 889B/3)
- Turnovers, 1940-1946 (Box 80B-81, 871)
  Turnovers provide a one sentence description of each story filmed, and the cameraman or creator who filmed it. They also distinguish which stories were used to create each newsreel, the date the newsreels were distributed to theaters, and which stories were vaulted.
  Arranged chronologically, with story numbers and volume & release numbers.
  - 39-571 to 42-612 [22/33 to 23/33], 1940 January 2-December 31 (Box-folder 80B/1)
  - 42-613 to 45-516 [23/34 to 24/34], 1941 January 2-December 31 (Box-folder 80B/2)
  - 45-517 to 48-243 [24/35 to 25/34], 1942 January 6-December 31 (Box-folder 80B/3)
  - 48-244 to 50-856 [25/35 to 26/35], 1943 January 5-December 31 (Box-folder 80B/4)
  - 50-857 to 52-899 [26/36 to 27/5], 1944 January 4-September 15 (Box-folder 80B/5)
  - 52-900 to 53-785 [27/6 to 27/36], 1944 September 20-December 30 (Box-folder 80B/6)
  - 53-786 to 56-799 [27/37 to 28/36], 1945 January 5-December 28 (Box-folder 81/1)
  - 56-800 to 60-141 [28/37 to 29/36], 1946 January 4-December 30 (Box-folder 81/2)
  - 39-571 to 42-612 [22/33 to 23/33], 1940 January 2-December 31, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/1)
  - 42-613 to 45-516 [23/34 to 24/34], 1941 January 2-December 31, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/2)
  - 45-517 to 48-243 [24/35 to 25/34], 1942 January 6-December 31, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/3)
  - 48-244 to 50-856 [25/35 to 26/35], 1943 January 5-December 31, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/4)
  - 50-857 to 53-785 [26/36 to 27/36], 1944 January 4-December 30, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/5)
  - 53-786 to 56-799 [27/37 to 28/36], 1945 January 5-December 28, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/6)
  - 56-800 to 60-141 [28/37 to 29/36], 1946 January 4-December 30, Photocopies. (Box-folder 871/7)